# Amartya Sengar

#### sengaramartya7@gmail.com

+91 6203854141

Delhi <u>LinkedIn</u> Github

I am currently a final-year student at Sharda University. I am pursuing a B- tech in Computer Science with a strong academic background. Java-savvy, proactive undergraduate with hands-on developer and human resource experience; always on the lookout for relevant challenges and continual learning.

EDUCATION B.Te

# B.Tech, Computer Science & Engineering

Sharda University

2020 - 2024

WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Sales Representative

NegBuy, Noida

Internship • May 2023 - Aug 2023 (3 months)

As a sales representative intern at Negbuy, my tasks include prospecting potential clients, presenting product offerings, negotiating deals, and ensuring customer satisfaction.

# **AWS Developer**

Amazon Web Services, Virtual

Internship • May 2022 - Aug 2022 (3 months)

I'd be coding alongside experienced engineers on projects that build, and improve AWS services Imagine working on new features for core AWS products, developing tools to manage cloud resources even contributing to the internal infrastructure that powers AWS

#### **SQL DEVELOPER**

Google Cloud, Virtual

Internship • Jun 2021 - Aug 2021 (3 months)

I code on cutting-edge cloud tech at Google Cloud! As a developer intern, I build new features, develop data tools for cloud resources, or analyze data to optimize performance.

**PROJECTS** 

#### Home automation system

Jun 2022 - Oct 2022

Our home automation system offers seamless control over devices, energy efficiency, security, and convenience. Experience modern living with smart technology tailored to your lifestyle.

#### College academic page

Mar 2021 - Oct 2021

Explore our diverse academic programs, meet our esteemed faculty, access essential resources, and benefit from comprehensive support services to thrive academically and personally. Welcome to our college's academic page.

# Identification of road deterioration entity using IOT for better navigation.

Aug 2023 - Present

Smart roads, smooth rides! This project uses the Internet of Things (IoT) to identify road damage, helping navigation apps reroute you and road crews fix problems faster. Drive smarter, drive safer!

WORK SAMPLES

### GitHub profile

https://github.com/amartyasen07

# Another portfolio link

https://github.com/amartyasen07/College-website

**SKILLS** 

MS-Word HTML
Advanced Advanced

CSS English Proficiency

(Spoken)

Intermediate Advanced

MS-Excel MS-PowerPoint

Advanced Advanced

MS SQL Server Java

Intermediate Intermediate

Arduino Artificial Intelligence

Intermediate Beginner

Software Testing Raspberry Pi

Intermediate Beginner

ADDITIONAL DETAILS

Oracle Java Foundation from Oracle., Completed All milestones in the Google Cloud Faciliatory Program, Completed all the milestones in AWS, Runner up in the quiz competition, and Interned in the RAS company.